让我听到你们的声音里也人民
一二    一二三
Now as the summer fades, I let you slip away
现在，随着夏季的褪色，我让你离开
You say I'm not your type, but I can make you sway
你说我不是你的适合类型，但我可以让你选择
It makes you burn to learn that you're not the only one
你难受的知道你并不是我的唯一
I'd let you be if you put down your blazin' gun
如果你放下（高贵），我会让你做自己
Now you've gone somewhere else, far away
现在，你已经有别的地方，远离我的地方
I don't know if I will find you (find you, find you)
我不知道是否能够找到你（找到你，找到你）
But you feel my breath on your neck
但是我感觉我的呼吸仍留在你的颈部
Can't believe I'm right behind you (right behind you)
不敢相信我就在你的身后（在你后面）
Cause you keep me coming back for more
因为你我回忆起了更多
And I feel a little better than I did before
我感觉比以前好些了
If I never see your face again, I don't mind
如果我再也看不到你的脸，我不介意
Cause we got much further than I thought we'd get tonight
因为我们今晚之间的距离已经比我想象的还要远
Sometimes you move so well it's hard not to give in
有时候你那么好，（让我）很难不对你妥协
I'm lost, I can't tell where you end and I begin
我迷失了，我不知道你是怎么结束的而我又是怎么开始的
It makes me burn to learn you're with another man
当我知道你与另一男子在一起，我心如焚烧
I wonder if he's half the lover that I am
我不知道他是否有我一半的好
Now you've gone somewhere else, far away
现在，你已经有别的地方，远离我的地方
I don't know if I will find you (find you, find you)
我不知道是否能够找到你（找到你，找到你）
But you feel my breath on your neck
但是我感觉我的呼吸仍留在你的颈部
Can't believe I'm right behind you (right behind you)
不敢相信我就在你的身后（在你后面）
Cause you keep me coming back for more
因为你我回忆起了更多
And I feel a little better than I did before
我感觉比以前好些了
If I never see your face again, I don't mind
如果我再也看不到你的脸，我不介意
Cause we got much further than I thought we'd get tonight
因为我们今晚之间的距离已经比我想象的还要远
Baby, baby, please believe me
宝贝，宝贝，请相信我
Find it in your heart to reach me
找到我在你心里的位置
Torture me by taking your time
占用你时间相当于对我实施酷刑
Promise not to leave me behind
答应我不要离开我
Take me down but take it easy
记住我但是放轻松
Make me think but don't decieve me
让我觉得你没有欺骗我
Cause  you keep me coming back for more
因为你我回忆起了更多
And I feel a little better than I did before
我感觉比以前好些了
If I never see your face again, I don't mind
如果我再也看不到你的脸，我不介意
Cause we got much further than I thought we'd get to me got to me
因为我们今晚之间的距离已经比我想象的还要远
Cause you keep me coming back for more
因为你我回忆起了更多
And I feel a little better than I did before
我感觉比以前好些了
If I never see your face again, I don't mind
如果我再也看不到你的脸，我不介意
Cause we got much further than I thought we'd get tonight
因为我们今晚之间的距离已经比我想象的还要远